zap.lu 2018-07-14

# Zap S.A. - Job

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. This website, www.zapsa.lu (the "Site"), is owned and operated by ZAP S.A. ("ZAP"). This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how we collect, use and disclose information that we may obtain about you ("You") ("Personal Information") through the Site. When You provide Personal Information to us via our Site, we protect it according to this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, You acknowledge that You have reviewed, and agree to, the terms of this Privacy Policy. If You do not agree to this Privacy Policy, do not use this Site.

ZAP S.A. adheres to the terms of the Luxembourg Law of 2 August 2002 on the protection of persons with respect to the processing of personal data.

To the extent we collect information online, our purpose is to better serve our business customers.

### The Personal Information We Collect

We may collect the following types of information when You browse this Site, any other website, or any affiliate site:

Personal Information You provide directly when You inquire about our services or via any email messages You send us, including personally identifiable information such as Your name, contact information (phone, fax and pager numbers, address, and email address). Personal Information You provide directly, including personally identifiable information You submit through this Site as part of the process of requesting information about the « Zap S.A. » services. Passively collected information, including through the use of "cookies" described below, such as IP addresses, web browser and operating system information, date and time of visits, and the web pages Your Internet browser visits when browsing this Site, any other ZAP website or any affiliate site; Click-through information related to ZAP S.A. emails and related marketing activities; and Aggregate, non-personally identifiable information, such as the number of hits per week or per web page.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are small text files that store information about Your interactions with a particular website, either temporarily (known as a "temporary" or "session" cookie, and deleted once You close Your browser window) or more permanently on the hard drive of Your computer (known as a "permanent" or "persistent cookie"). Cookies can make it easier to use a website by allowing servers to access certain information quickly.

### Web Beacons

ZAP S.A. may use "web beacon" technology to gather metrics from anonymous web users and email recipients for the purpose of operating and improving websites and email communications. A web beacon is an electronic image that is imbedded in a web page or email which allows to track web page views/hits or the opening of an email containing a beacon. ZAP may use web beacon in conjunction with cookies to track web site activity on www.zapsa.lu and associated websites. Web beacon tracking by ZAP S.A. does not identify the name or email address of the web user or mail recipient.

### The Way We Use Personal Information

ZAP uses Personal Information You have provided directly or information we collect indirectly online about You for marketing purposes in the following ways: For Personal Information You provide directly online, or through email messages, relating to inquiries about our services, we use the information to engage in and process transactions with You, to respond to Your inquiries and requests, to provide information on our services and to provide customer support activities. Before we use Your Personal Information, we will give You the opportunity to choose whether or not You allow ZAP S.A. to use Your Personal Information in such ways described in this Privacy Policy. You may at any time choose to stop receiving ZAP's emails relating to our marketing materials by following the unsubscribing instructions contained in the emails we send to Your attention. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email to [contact@zap.lu](mailto:contact@zap.lu) and requesting the removal of Your name from our marketing lists.

For Personal Information You provide online, including actions or clicks from hyperlinks and subscriptions, we may use the information to customize future communications and web pages in accordance with communication preferences You have established with us.  
For Personal Information about web pages visited, page hits per week, and the like, we use this information internally to improve the design of our web pages.  
For Personal Information submitted using the online job application process, we may use and disseminate this information internally and among our affiliates as necessary to consider Your application and to contact You regarding our decision.

### When We Share Your Personal Information

ZAP S.A. shares information for business and marketing purposes only on a need-to-know basis and only with: (a) our own employees, contingent workers, (b) ZAP’s subcontractors, consultants, and third-party service-provider companies, that have agreed to safeguard such information in a like manner to the way that safeguards such information and that have agreed to confidentiality terms with us or that have entered into arrangements with us to provide the services described in this privacy policy; and (c) other entities authorized to have access to such information under applicable law or regulation.  
ZAP may disclose Your Personal Information to protect our rights or property, to enforce our terms of use and legal notices, as required or permitted by law, or at the request of government regulators or other law enforcement officials and the courts. We shall have no duty to notify You of such compliance with local law.  
ZAP S.A. will not use or share Your Personal Information in ways unrelated to those described above without first notifying You and offering You a choice as to whether or not we may use Your Personal Information in a different manner. ZAP does not share non-public personally identifiable information with third party marketers.

### Our Commitment to Data Integrity and Security

ZAP S.A. is committed to protecting Your privacy. ZAP processes Your Personal Information only in ways compatible with the purpose for which it was collected. To the extent necessary for such purposes, we take reasonable steps to make sure that the information is accurate, complete, current and otherwise reliable with regard to its intended use. However, ZAP expects that You will update their personal information with ZAP as necessary.  
ZAP S.A. takes reasonable and appropriate measures to maintain the confidentiality and integrity, and prevent the unauthorized use or disclosure, of information. This includes maintaining a system of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards to secure such information.

### Links to Unaffiliated Third Party Websites

This Site may contain links to affiliated and unaffiliated third party websites. If You link to or otherwise visit any other websites managed by third parties, ZAP S.A. encourages You to review the privacy policies that may be available on these websites. You understand that ZAP has no control over those websites and is not responsible or liable for the policies and practices followed by such third parties.

### How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information

You can request access to Your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain, and update or correct that information, through e-mailing. To protect Your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify Your identity before granting access or making corrections. We may keep information in an off-line form, for archival purposes or as otherwise required by law. Please note that if Your information is removed from our databases, You may no longer be able to access certain areas of our website requiring registration or a subscription. Users may request to be removed from our e-mail list, by following the "unsubscribe" instructions on e-mails from ZAP or by sending a request to [contact@zap.lu](mailto:contact@zap.lu)

### Revisions and Contact Information

We periodically update the features of our Site to better serve You and all our customers. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without advance notice and any modifications are effective when they are posted here. The date of the newest version will be posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before You submit any personally identifiable information at this Site, to see if the Privacy Policy has changed. By using our website, You indicate Your understanding and acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy posted at the time of Your use. If You have any questions, please contact us by sending an e-mail message to [contact@zap.lu](mailto:contact@zap.lu)

Privacy Policy - May 4th 2015
### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. This website, www.zapsa.lu (the "Site"), is owned and operated by ZAP S.A. ("ZAP"). This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how we collect, use and disclose information that we may obtain about you ("You") ("Personal Information") through the Site. When You provide Personal Information to us via our Site, we protect it according to this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, You acknowledge that You have reviewed, and agree to, the terms of this Privacy Policy. If You do not agree to this Privacy Policy, do not use this Site.

ZAP S.A. adheres to the terms of the Luxembourg Law of 2 August 2002 on the protection of persons with respect to the processing of personal data.

To the extent we collect information online, our purpose is to better serve our business customers.

### The Personal Information We Collect

We may collect the following types of information when You browse this Site, any other website, or any affiliate site:

Personal Information You provide directly when You inquire about our services or via any email messages You send us, including personally identifiable information such as Your name, contact information (phone, fax and pager numbers, address, and email address). Personal Information You provide directly, including personally identifiable information You submit through this Site as part of the process of requesting information about the « Zap S.A. » services. Passively collected information, including through the use of "cookies" described below, such as IP addresses, web browser and operating system information, date and time of visits, and the web pages Your Internet browser visits when browsing this Site, any other ZAP website or any affiliate site; Click-through information related to ZAP S.A. emails and related marketing activities; and Aggregate, non-personally identifiable information, such as the number of hits per week or per web page.

### Cookies

"Cookies" are small text files that store information about Your interactions with a particular website, either temporarily (known as a "temporary" or "session" cookie, and deleted once You close Your browser window) or more permanently on the hard drive of Your computer (known as a "permanent" or "persistent cookie"). Cookies can make it easier to use a website by allowing servers to access certain information quickly.

### Web Beacons

ZAP S.A. may use "web beacon" technology to gather metrics from anonymous web users and email recipients for the purpose of operating and improving websites and email communications. A web beacon is an electronic image that is imbedded in a web page or email which allows to track web page views/hits or the opening of an email containing a beacon. ZAP may use web beacon in conjunction with cookies to track web site activity on www.zapsa.lu and associated websites. Web beacon tracking by ZAP S.A. does not identify the name or email address of the web user or mail recipient.

### The Way We Use Personal Information

ZAP uses Personal Information You have provided directly or information we collect indirectly online about You for marketing purposes in the following ways: For Personal Information You provide directly online, or through email messages, relating to inquiries about our services, we use the information to engage in and process transactions with You, to respond to Your inquiries and requests, to provide information on our services and to provide customer support activities. Before we use Your Personal Information, we will give You the opportunity to choose whether or not You allow ZAP S.A. to use Your Personal Information in such ways described in this Privacy Policy. You may at any time choose to stop receiving ZAP's emails relating to our marketing materials by following the unsubscribing instructions contained in the emails we send to Your attention. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email to [contact@zap.lu](mailto:contact@zap.lu) and requesting the removal of Your name from our marketing lists.

For Personal Information You provide online, including actions or clicks from hyperlinks and subscriptions, we may use the information to customize future communications and web pages in accordance with communication preferences You have established with us.  
For Personal Information about web pages visited, page hits per week, and the like, we use this information internally to improve the design of our web pages.  
For Personal Information submitted using the online job application process, we may use and disseminate this information internally and among our affiliates as necessary to consider Your application and to contact You regarding our decision.

### When We Share Your Personal Information

ZAP S.A. shares information for business and marketing purposes only on a need-to-know basis and only with: (a) our own employees, contingent workers, (b) ZAP’s subcontractors, consultants, and third-party service-provider companies, that have agreed to safeguard such information in a like manner to the way that safeguards such information and that have agreed to confidentiality terms with us or that have entered into arrangements with us to provide the services described in this privacy policy; and (c) other entities authorized to have access to such information under applicable law or regulation.  
ZAP may disclose Your Personal Information to protect our rights or property, to enforce our terms of use and legal notices, as required or permitted by law, or at the request of government regulators or other law enforcement officials and the courts. We shall have no duty to notify You of such compliance with local law.  
ZAP S.A. will not use or share Your Personal Information in ways unrelated to those described above without first notifying You and offering You a choice as to whether or not we may use Your Personal Information in a different manner. ZAP does not share non-public personally identifiable information with third party marketers.

### Our Commitment to Data Integrity and Security

ZAP S.A. is committed to protecting Your privacy. ZAP processes Your Personal Information only in ways compatible with the purpose for which it was collected. To the extent necessary for such purposes, we take reasonable steps to make sure that the information is accurate, complete, current and otherwise reliable with regard to its intended use. However, ZAP expects that You will update their personal information with ZAP as necessary.  
ZAP S.A. takes reasonable and appropriate measures to maintain the confidentiality and integrity, and prevent the unauthorized use or disclosure, of information. This includes maintaining a system of appropriate administrative, physical and technical safeguards to secure such information.

### Links to Unaffiliated Third Party Websites

This Site may contain links to affiliated and unaffiliated third party websites. If You link to or otherwise visit any other websites managed by third parties, ZAP S.A. encourages You to review the privacy policies that may be available on these websites. You understand that ZAP has no control over those websites and is not responsible or liable for the policies and practices followed by such third parties.

### How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information

You can request access to Your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain, and update or correct that information, through e-mailing. To protect Your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify Your identity before granting access or making corrections. We may keep information in an off-line form, for archival purposes or as otherwise required by law. Please note that if Your information is removed from our databases, You may no longer be able to access certain areas of our website requiring registration or a subscription. Users may request to be removed from our e-mail list, by following the "unsubscribe" instructions on e-mails from ZAP or by sending a request to [contact@zap.lu](mailto:contact@zap.lu)

### Revisions and Contact Information

We periodically update the features of our Site to better serve You and all our customers. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without advance notice and any modifications are effective when they are posted here. The date of the newest version will be posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before You submit any personally identifiable information at this Site, to see if the Privacy Policy has changed. By using our website, You indicate Your understanding and acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy posted at the time of Your use. If You have any questions, please contact us by sending an e-mail message to [contact@zap.lu](mailto:contact@zap.lu)

Privacy Policy - May 4th 2015
